Thank you for watching!
Hello everyone.
Hello.
Ukka's,
A delightful, fluffy showroom.
Yay.
Yes. Good evening, everyone.
We're Uka.
Yes. Today's host is,
I, Seri-chan, will be your host today.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Omichami.
That's right. Omichami.
Roo-chan introduces herself.
I dyed my hair. I'm Lou Aoe.
He's so cool.
She's cute. It looks good on you.
Next?
Next? I'm Miyamoto Fine Arts. Pleased to meet you.
Please do.
Mr. Miyamoto, Ms. Miyamoto, myself and Ruru-chan will be presenting today.
Please take care of us.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you for watching the 188th Ukwa's Delightful and Funny Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So, I would like to take this time to spread the word.
I would like to have a spread time here,
Yes.
What would you like to say?
Today,
I want to have this today.
Oh, that's right.
The goods we're going to sell at TWOFU.
Me, Risa and..,
Sora and..,
With Apie,
Ayumi,With Ayumi,
Uichan.
Ayumi and Ui-chan. This is the first time for us to sell our products,
It's our first time, not our first time, but it's been a while, right?
Yes, it has been a while.
Please get one and do this, do this, do this.
Yes. Like this is for me.
Do you want to hold this?
Makeup towels are a little tight. I can't hold it right now.
That's true.
What shall we say?
What shall we do?
How about, "Look at me, Mr. What's wrong with you?
I'll put it in.
Or you can use the name of the diaper... or whoever you want.
What do you say, Rui, look at me.
Riju-chan, look at me!
I'd be happy if you could comment on it in any way you like.
I'd be happy to do it.
So...
What do you think?
I'd love to hear from you.
Well, when you get here...
I'm Yukirinu.
Yukirinu.
Shall we go?
Let's go!
How's it going? How's it going? How's it going? You like it?
Yeah, it's good.
Okay, five, four, three, two, one.
Goldfish.
That's good.
So, this is it. Please shop around.
I'll introduce you later.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Please retweet us.
So, we performed at the Rock Hong Gyidol Festival 2023 on July 30,
It's been a year since I've been?
It hasn't been a year. I performed for the first time at a ping-pong festival last time.
It's been a year.
I was very happy.
So you are all going to be in this one?
That's the motto that everyone made up last year, I think.
Something like this.
That's the way to do it.
We did it.
So, it was the first time for me to be there, and I remember it was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Just as you wish.
It was fun.
But we had a rare lunchtime tie, I guess you would call it.
I think it was a lunchtime tie, but we did a live show,
Four songs, right?
Four songs.
It was really hot, wasn't it?
It was very hot. It felt like summer.
It was really hot in the daytime, so it felt hot.
The sun wasn't shining, though,
That's right. The sun wasn't shining.
The heat was doubled.
It was really fun. Thank you very much.
I personally got to do a karaoke collaboration afterwards.
The music had to have a star in the name.
That's not a requirement.
I was chosen for such a group,
We sang Bish's "Hoshi ga Matataku Yoru ni" (On a Starry Night).
We were told that Bish would sing at the center.
The song was decided on the day of the event.
Really?Is that so?
We had originally decided to do a song about the stars,
I had heard some candidates. So you heard some of them.
So you heard some songs. So I had heard some candidate songs.
But we chose one of them on the day of the concert.
Really?
I had heard that we were all going to sing together,
But 20 minutes before the show, I looked back on my solo part.
Really?
I looked at her face.
I was so nervous.
Thank you so much for your hard work!
But it was almost the first time for me to sing and dance with other group members.
So it was a lot of fun.
So it was a lot of fun and I was very happy.
It was my first memory.
There were such events, too.
Yesterday, August 1, was the 8th anniversary of Uka's debut!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
I am different from Ruri,
I am also Riru, Sora and Ayumi.
Riru, Sora and Ayumi performed at Tokyo Address Festival for the first time 8 years ago,
That was the day Uka made her debut,
How was it?
What does a year feel like?
Eight years ago, I was 12 years old, in the first year of junior high school,
I didn't know what was right or left,
I couldn't remember much,
I remember those days,
I was in the wrong position on the day of the show.
I was in the "smiley girl" group at first.
And then I sang, but I was in the wrong position.
I made a mistake.
I said I would do my best on stage and not make any mistakes.And I told him that I would do my best on the stage.
I remember saying, "I'll do my best on the stage,
I am so thankful that we are able to continue to do this,
I am very thankful that I am able to continue to do so, and I am grateful to everyone for their support,
I also want to thank everyone for their constant support.
How about you, Nuri-chan?
Nine years, huh?
You have been with us for two years.
It's been a little over a year for me.
I've been here for about 10 months,
I felt happy to be able to be a part of such a long history,
I hope we can continue to do so together in the future.
That's really true.
I listened to it once.
Momochan also received one.
I was one of the first members to join the group,
When I first joined,
I had to take part in lessons and so on,
There was nothing I could do.
So, I had no choice,
And I am a bad omen,
It's hard just to keep doing this for 8 years or 1 year,
For me.
But for me, it's a challenge just to keep doing this for 8 years or even 1 year,
Of course, it's the members,
And of course, the staff members as well,
I think I am able to keep doing this because I enjoy it,
I will continue to be the only one who never gets tired of it,
It's not a hobby,
It's not a hobby, but it's the only thing I never get tired of,
It's not a hobby, but it's the only thing that I never get tired of, and it's fun.
I hope you all will continue to support me.
Momochan was 9 years old.
Nine years old and growing up.I'll be 9 years old and growing up.
When my next birthday comes,
It's a Friday before my birthday,
I will have been there for more than half of my life,
I've been there for more than half of my life.
So, please take good care of this.
Thank you very much.
Thank you all.
Thank you all for the many congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much. So, I'm going to say this,
As I introduced earlier,
I have just introduced our goods to be sold at the TOKYO AIDA FESTIVAL,
The first one is the fan I mentioned earlier,
The first one is the fan I mentioned earlier.
I wonder if it is called an uchiwa (fan).
It has our names written on the back.
All of them have different colors.
Sora's is orange and blue, and Rin's is yellow and bluish.
If it was Rin, it would be yellow and blue.
They are all different.
Also, isn't it unusual to have such a beautiful woman?
Yes, they are.
Because of Momo-chan's hairstyle.
Ayame's is the only one I know. I know her hair style well.
That's for sure.
I've never really had a cuff up,
I've only started to like it recently,
So I'm surprised to see it as a popular item.
That's true. I also like my hair parted on the side.
It looks mature.
My bangs are parted too.
It's a little unusual.
Sora is quite mature, too.
I have an image of Sora as an adult.
It's nice. Please lyricize it, everyone.That's good. Please everyone, please lyric it.
Please do.
And, please, please, please,
What can I say, I'm waiting for it,
I think it's going to be very slow,
I think I have something for you.
That's the towel with the famous quotes.
The towel of words of wisdom.
First of all, let's put ourselves out.
Ah, this way.
I found mine.
Then theirs.
What's your quote, Ruri?
Loosen.
Oh, that's it.
Cute and gummy is wonderful.
That's it.
I see.
Well, I thought it was Ruri and all kinds of writing.
It's nice.
I think it's a sentence that expresses Ruri to the fullest.
I like the way she poses,
I'm posing like this, and I'm posing behind you, like I'm cute, right?
It's a pose, isn't it?
Is it okay?
It's like that.
I see. That's good.
That's good. Nice words.
Here's a towel with a quote.
And it has my name on the bottom right.
It's easy to understand.
Nice. And the colors,
Blue and white.
Very nice.
It's true.Certainly.
By all means.
I hope you all will, too, after you get it.
I'm sure you'll get it, too.
Yes, I agree.
Okay, Riji-san.
Yes, I am. I have been saying this every day.
I say this every day, too.
This way.
Let's work hard together tomorrow, too.
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice. And this,
I was thinking, that serve of yours, Riji-chan.
I always thought of you as a healer.
Even though your expression is also healing.
Like, "Let's do our best.
That's right.
But, you know, the letters...
I think it's a bit too much.
It's a bit of a "wasshoi" type of thing.
I'll show you mine.
I'd be happy to show you mine.
The difference in handwriting.
Even here.
There's a big difference in the number of letters.
It's long.
But it's very Riji-chan-like.
Thank you very much for this one.
I hope you'll come this way, too. Let's look at it and work hard together.
Let's do our best.
I'm glad you liked it.
I hope you all know who I am.
You all know who I am, don't you?
It's Barbilon.
This is absolutely...
Before the concert. Not before the live.Before the live. Not before the gig.
After the concert.
I'm going to say this one last thing.
I'm sure you've heard me say "barbellone" a lot, haven't you?
I said it a lot, didn't I?
Then I did this.
I'd like to have you say it at the end of the show.
If you even say "Laiby"...
When I say "Livy"...
I would want to get a loan.
Like, "Here's just a loan.
That's for sure.
Shall I say it again?
Rone.
It's nice to see their faces.
Yes, it is.
By all means.
This will be in front of us too.
That's right.
Shall I introduce the three members who are not here?
Let's start from there.
Ayame...
Good morning, world.
Ayame is also on Twitter.
Ayame posts
Ayame posts every day.
Twitter.
Please leave your comments.
If you use this as a header for Ayame-chan and her friends...
It looks really good, doesn't it?
I like it.
I don't know what it is.
It would be nice.
When I wake up, I wake up and say "Good morning world.
Good morning, world.
I'm happy.I am happy.
By all means.
Next time, I'm going to go to the restaurant.
Here it is.
You look great.
Oh.
You look like Sora.
Sora-like.
You're nice.
You're wonderful.
Can you encourage me with this?
Sure.
You should get one.
It's nice.
Wouldn't you want them to be displayed one by one?
Sure.
I want them all in my room.
That's nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
You are nice.
I kind of saw Yuki-san.
I don't really get it.
Yes, let's be amazed.
What do you mean?
No, but you look like him.
You look like Yuki-san.
I'm going to get pampered.
You look like Rina-chan.
Let's get pampered.
It's summery.
It's true.
It looks like Rina-chan.
I bet you think so. So do you, Rina.
I think she's probably thinking it.
She's thinking about it.
She's thinking, "Let's be loved.I'm thinking, "Let's get amused.
I think it's good.
Please ask Hana-chan for the truth.
I guess so.
I don't know.
When I asked Rina-chan what she meant by "let's be together"...
Rina-chan just said
Violence.
I'm sure she'll listen to me.
I hope you all will come too.
I will be appearing at TIFF on August 4 and 6,
I'll be appearing at TIFF on August 4 and 6, and the tickets will be on sale from that TIFF,
Please check it out.
So that's it,
I guess it looks like this.
It's like this.
Our recent activities, or rather..,
I mean, an announcement,
Thank you for your patience.
So...,
I would like to go to the project here.
Today is a bit difficult.
Difficult? I don't know.
Let's go.
Today we are going to do a project like this.
A special summer event,
Let's play SHOWROOM's original game!
Yay!
It's a special event.
What?
There isn't such a thing, is there?
It's the bus vacation.
So..,
On July 4, SHOWROOM released a new
a distribution tool for V-livers.Distribution tools for V-libbers
Mini-game in peralev
I would like to play with SHOWROOM Shooting.
Apparently, this game
the cooperation of our listeners is essential, so
Please keep your eyes on us.
If you clear the game, we are
will get a cold sweet, so let's eat it!
Let's eat it!
I want to eat it!
Great.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat it. It's hot.
Okay, first of all.
What kind of game is SHOWROOM SHOOTING?
Please watch this VTR.
SHOWROOM Shooting
Oh, now
Cute bear
Four difficulty levels.
And that's 13 games too many.
That's right. Glad to hear it.
Bear.
Oh, my God.
It's like Burn.
Hey.
Experience
It's an experience.
time
It's a bear.
It's not a bear.
It's how it operates.
I mean...
I see.
It's like if you're running away, you're not running away, you're dodging, you're automatically shooting.It's kinda like if you're already running away, you're not running away, you're dodging and the shooter automatically shoots.
Oh, it's strong!
Strong, strong, strong!
And this is what we're going to do when we deliver,
It'll come out,
It's fun, isn't it?
It's fun to watch, isn't it?
Bear is getting mad at me.
Oh, my gosh.
He's mad, he's mad, he's mad.
But there's more to make him angry.
Oh, I'm getting tired.
What's that?
Hang in there.
What is it?
Wow, you're getting stronger all at once.
Amazing.
You won.
Congratulations!
We're all going to work together to defeat the big bear.
We're going to defeat the big bear by working together.
First of all, you're good at games.
I'm good at games, or maybe I like games
Both
I think I'll ask the board members
On the viewer's side.
Depending on the gift you throw.
the attack changes and the member gets to eat sweets.
I see what you mean.
I want to eat.
Time to explain what it means.
I'll do my best.
Good luck, Mr. Director.
I'll start from the normal level.I'll do it from the normal level.
I'll do my best.
I'm glad
You're right about the director.
I'm amazing.
Oh, Ao-chan...
You're so cut out!
Chancellor...
I'm a little nervous.
I can practice a little now.
You're moving.
Thank you.
Daruma did it.
Up and down, up and down.
Back and forth.
Thank you guys.
Good luck.
I'm a little nervous.
Here they come.
They're here.
Oh, my God.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's a heart.
It'll heal my HP.
Oh!
Good luck.
That's good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's pretty good.
It's taking a lot of time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How's it coming?How's it going?
Hold on.
Thank you, Mr. Kako.
Which one is it?
The pink one?
Pink.
They say you're the best, Lil.
Are you sure?
He's mad.
Finally.
We're about halfway there.
That doesn't sound good.
He's angry.
Oh, it's gone.
When I'm angry...
Right now.
It's amazing.
Oh, look.
I'm nervous.
I'm so nervous.
But we're almost there.
I can do it. I can do it.
Almost there.
I got it.
Liz, you're clear.
We did it!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Can I open this? Can I open it later?
Is this a cold sweet?
It won't open.
It's open.
It's jelly.Jelly.
Looks delicious. What jelly?
Mango jelly.
Yay! Thank you very much.
Thank you all. For your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
I want to win.
Thank you for watching.
How was it?
It's been a long time since I played computer games,
I used to play shooting games when I was little,
I was nervous because it was my first time,
But it was fun,
I'm glad I won. Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
As a gamer, I have to win,
I have to win.
So, which way do you want to go next?
Have you ever been to a computer game?
Elementary school or sushi?
Which one?
Mao. I don't know.
Let's just go there.
Let's go in the middle.
You want to go that way?
That's not how you use a computer,
It's the way you use it, isn't it?
The machine.
Well, good luck, Momoa-chan.
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
Then, let's start.
Oh, I like Wacha.
Wacha likes spiders.
Wacha has a spider.
Something a little bit, I couldn't get the spider in Asha's way.I couldn't get a spider in some kind of asha way.
Right here, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Good luck, Ma-chan.
Thank you.
Go for it!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Thank you, Daruma!
Amazing!
Mar-chan's Daruma bricks are falling apart!
This is a Daruma afa, right?
He's doing it.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there!
But...
Oh, no!
Oh, up
Go for it
There is no count
Hang in there, hang in there
But no thanks, give it back already good from the beginning
Kubo, when you throw, hold on
When Kaga-san throws, throw hard!
Amazing!
You're invincible!
Invincible!
I'm going to throw a lot!
Yikes!
Thank you!
Congratulations!
We won!
That's great!
Thank you!
I got one too!
Oh! Yay!
What? I don't know... you looked amazing.What? I don't know...she looked amazing.
Mo-chan turned into a bear!
Hey!
Mo-chan turned into a bear.
Oh, it was LaFrance jelly.
Oh!
The same!
LaFrance.
Bon appétit.
Thank you! You did it.
Congratulations.
Yay!
Well, Ruri.
I have to do it!
I'm the only one who got a cold one.
Don't worry, Ruri.
Do your best!
I'll do my best!
But I've been playing a lot of games too,
Like Atsumori.
Atsumori and so on.
Not Atsumori.
Atsumori?
Oh, no.
Ending
The next preview
Thank goodness Dharma-chan is ready to throw even from the beginning!
That's great!
Woohoo!
Go for it!
Oh, I did it!
So many!
I think there's some kind of bear or something.
Here.
Oh!Ah!
A-ha-ha-ha!
I'm afraid when it's gone until now
A-ha-ha-ha
Oh, no, it's close, it's close, it's close
Close, close, close
It's getting closer.
That was fast!
Yay!
Thank you very much. Yay! We got Sweets.
Congratulations.
We won.
First things first,
What flavor?
L'Oeufrance delicatessen.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
That's great. It means we're clear.
But I'm quite proud,
It's not like you won because you thought you were going to lose,
It was difficult because I was able to win,
I was in the "normal" mode, so I'm going to go with "difficult".
I might like to give it a try.
How about it? Okay, Ariji-san, let's go.
Let's start with the first one.
Difficult.
It looks difficult.
Difficult sounds difficult.
Difficult looks difficult.
The bear looks strong.
It looks strong.
But I was able to win earlier.
Well, if we keep it up.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Okay, so I did the normal one earlier,
I would like to try the difficult one.
Good luck.
All right. I'll do my best.
I made a mistake.
How's it going.
Eh...
Thank you.
Thank you three for being awesome.
Like this.
I see.
Thank you very much.
I heard there's going to be an increase in rank.
Oh!
Petal.
Oh, bear, it's daddy bear.
How hard can it be?
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, no, no, no!
I want to win, don't you?
I want to do my best
Marumasan...
Okay, here we go
But...
It's early. Is it early?
Oh, that's what I mean
It's early.
Wait, wait, wait.
I think I'm at 100.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Bears.
If you're a bear, you're in attack mode.
You're in attack mode.
I'm in attack mode. I'm in attack mode.Your opponent is in attack mode.
Your opponent's cover is dwindling.
I'm in a bear, but I'm still a bear.
I can do a double.
He's angry.
He's mad.
Isn't that a hoo-ha?
Is that a wolf?
Oh!
Yeah!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
It's clear, guys! Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
How do you feel about it?
Well, I used a lot of bears, but when it got hard, it was all at once,
But when you get to the hardest level, the enemies and their attacks get faster and bigger,
It was a little difficult, but thanks to all of you, I was able to win.
Thanks to all of you, I was able to win.
I hope you will try it too.
Thank you very much.
Please give it a try.
So that's that,
That's why,
I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry.
I'd like to invite you all to come to the showroom shooting.
Can we progress on a moment's notice?
Please try Showroom Shooting.
That's all for now, let's play the original showroom game.
So, I would like to go to the next project.
The next project is this project.
Don't have fun in Yukkari! Ukkaji PT.
Have you heard of the recently popular chat GPT?
I might be new to it.
Really? There is a service called "Chat GPT" which can answer any question instantly by artificial intelligence,Really? There is a service called "Chat GPT" which can answer any question instantly by artificial intelligence,
This time, we would like to have a Ugkaji PT to compete with the Chat GPT.
Please feel free to ask us any questions you may have in the comments on the Ugkaja PT.
We will answer anyway.
By the way, since Mr. Ebichu has a room in the Ebichu GPT, we are going to have a Ugkaja PT as well,
Please comment a lot.
Have I always done this?
I've never done it before.
Have I done it once?
Really?
Have you ever done this in a showroom?
Maybe once.
Maybe?
So, you're willing to believe anything as soon as it comes to you in the comments?
I'm like Mr. D.
So let's get to it, shall we?
I guess so.
What do you guys want to ask me?
Do you have a question?
What should we do for dinner tonight?
Oh, Cascón!
That's it!
Is that right?
Yes, it fits! That's what I mean by "it fits"!
What's the weather like on Tiff's day?
Sunny! Sunny! Nothing but sunshine!
Sunny! Clear! Clear!
What time should I go to bed today? Twelve o'clock!
Oh! That's early!
Sleep is important! Yes, I know!
Let's see, what's the food for the festival?
Chocolate bananas!
Yakisoba! cotton candy!
Oh! Great, you three answer!Oooh!!! Great, you three answer me!
Something, something, something! That's reasonable!
Good, good, good!
What month is it today? Oh, August!
Oh, that's not good! Oh, yeah!
It's August! That's no good!
Aisaku Natsuri is a tanning club!
It's not a tanning club! Yakimasa!
Little piece fan!
Hat!
This is funny!
Can I start with you, Ruri?
What color do you want to dye your hair?
The same!
Inner color!
Blonde hair on the bottom!
Like Ayami-chan!
I really envy you! So cute!
I love it! It suits me!
What idols do you recommend? Uka.
Uka.
But this is Uka.
That's right. Uka. On the contrary, he asked us this.
That's right.
Recommended for idols.
Which member of Uka has the best sense?
Riju-chan.
Me?
Me.
Riju-chan. She's the best of all women.
Isn't that somehow the most interesting thing in Uka?
Like a ranking in Uka.
I wonder what else it is.
Are you going out this Sunday?Are you going to play this Sunday?
Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff is all I have.
Who goes to bed early in Ukka?
Ayame.
Not until they fall asleep, but in time.
If I were to say by time, I would say Ayame.
I think Solo is the one who falls asleep the fastest.
I think so too.
It's certainly early.
I imagine that if I go to sleep right away, I'm already in deep sleep.
I don't even notice it.
What is this? Speaking of the backstage banjo of Ukka.
What's "backstage banjo"?
Who is the loudest person in the dressing room?
Ereli.
Excuse me.
You.
What is it?
You seem like you'd be a pain in the ass to hang out with.
I wonder what it is. Wait.
I've got to go get ready first thing.
Um, Mizuki.
What?
You seem to have a lot of lines.
Ayame.
Sora.
It's okay that I'm here, but I won't have you say it's a hassle.
I don't want you to say it's a hassle because there are a lot of lines right now,
You mean as a girlfriend.
That makes sense.
Who is the smartest person in Uka?
Rina-chan.
Who's always eating sweets?Who always eats sweets?
Momochan
Lurin
Rina, Moa-chan.
I find food interesting.
It sure is.
Do you want to try it?
Sure, no problem.
Who has the most luggage? Sora. Sola. I have an image that your carry-on case is bigger than other people's.
What do you put in it? I've recently added a carry-on case to my luggage. Can you carry it? But you didn't say you can't fit in it? But you know, if my carry-on is this big, Sola's is this big.
What are you carrying? What's the craziest thing in vodka? I don't know. Maybe Rina. What's that? I don't know.
I might be Ruri. Who has the most idol friends in Ukka? Ayume.
Who has the least luggage? I think Moa.
I'm Ayame.
Ayame for sure.
I used to carry hundreds of yen and a lot of stuff.
I'm in the plus side these days, aren't I?
Yes, I have.
It was recommended to me.
I put the pack on top of my carry-on.
Yes, that's right.
Is there anything else?
People always arrive at the last minute.
Wow, that depends on the day.
Depends on the day.
I think Ayame is the early one.
That's for sure.
There you go.
But I sometimes do it too.
Sora is quite extreme.
Sometimes she's very fast, and sometimes she stays at it for 30 minutes,
And sometimes really fast, and sometimes a little bit slower.
It's true, isn't it? It's possible.
This sounds interesting.
Uka, this is Uka.
Where would you like to go on tour?Where would you like to tour?
Somewhere in Shikoku.
Ah.
I'd like to go somewhere. I've never been to Shikoku.
I'm sure you're right.
Hokkaido.
Uh... Hiroshima.
That's pretty far back.
It's backstreet.
Backstreet.
It's in the backstreets.
Can you say all prefectures in Shikoku?
Ehime
Tokushima.
No?
Correct.
Anna Shinkai?
Hiroshima.
Ehime.
The moment he said "Shikoku", the air was filled with excitement.
I don't remember the song anymore.
I wrote it myself.
What song?
Ehime, Hiroshima, Tokushima.
I have songs in my head.
That's great.
I like it. I like the way you remember.
something
And then there's
A lowered voice of confidence
And then there's...
What was that?
Where do you want to go? Overseas?
Hawaii!Hawaii!
Italy?
Guam!
Oh!
Group terrier!
That's right.
Of course.
What song?
I wrote it myself.
Oh, wow.
The one from earlier.
Well, I wonder what else it's about.
What kind of ice cream do you like? The kind you like to taste?
I mean choux, mango.
Vanilla and cookie.
Chocolate.
Yes, and this one.
I see. This is interesting.
I think we'll probably split into two.
Who can remember the moves the fastest?
I bet.
Ah! I guess we'll have to split up.
I'll go.
Ayame. I think I'm Ayame too.
Ayame. Ayame is Solo, right?
I had two choices. I had two choices, too.
What is your favorite season?
Autumn!
The winter tan is so nice.
It's so nice.
Spring?
Winter.
Oh, I see.
We're divided, aren't we?
We're divided.
And what do you recommend the best Doraemon tool?What other Doraemon tools do you recommend the most?
Ankipan
It's facing this way.
It's got something in it.
Just because it's in there, it's in there.
It sure is.
This looks interesting.
The second loudest one...
I'm not going to do number one.
Done.
Seino
Rina.
Not so loud anymore.
It's not big anymore.
You're right, you're right, you're right.
It's a little embarrassing.
It comes out unexpectedly, sometimes.
You mean you're reacting too loudly?
That's good, that's good, that's good.
It's definitely Rina.
Rina's big.
Rina-chan, isn't it?
Rina-chan's reaction to everything.
Rina-chan's reaction.
She's like, "Wow!" when I say "wow!
It's quite a surprise, isn't it?
That's true.
I'd like you to pour it on me.
It looks delicious. Do you want some?
I'd love a drink.
It looks good.
That's a first.
Isn't this a chat GP, too?
That's what I thought.That kind of opinion.
I'll have to tell you soon.
What's the longest sleep you've ever had?
In the bedroom, right?
I've never heard of that.
That's for sure.
Depends on the day.
But I think it's Ayame.
She seems to have the most regular life.
She seems to go to bed early.
She also gets up early in the morning.
So I think she takes her time to sleep.
She seems to be regular.
That's for sure.
I think so.
What do you think?
Good night.
If it was a side, it would be the other day.
That's right.
What do you want to do in August?
Is it okay if it doesn't come true?
I want to go to a river or something.
I want to do something fun.
That's good.
I'm not going, and I might not do it, but I'm hoping for a pool slide, you know?
That one!
Shoe is surprisingly good.
I want to do the auto slide.
Do you want to go?
I'm not going.
Go?
I'm for everyone to come.
Suddenly.
I want people to come to the concert.
Yes, okay.Yes, I understand.
Please come, everyone.
Yes, that's it, that's all for now, a pleasant and hilarious Ukkajin PT.
Thank you very much.
Now to the ending.
The ending came so fast this time, but today's game was a star. Really.
It all happened so fast.
Let me explain.
On September 30, Crescendo reaches Beats Shibuya.
On October 14, Déjà Vu will be at Tokyo Kinema Club.
Yes, it will be a live performance.
I'm sure you've all signed up, but if you haven't yet, I'd appreciate it if you could add it to your schedule.
Please do so.
Yes, OK.
I will be making an additional appearance on Tiff2023.
Friday, August 8, from 10:00 a.m., T-shirt collaboration stage.
Heatgarde. Oh, no.
Heat Garage.
And from 11:35 am, Doll Factory.
From 1:50 p.m. is the Hot Stage.
Not this time.
On August 4, we will be performing on three stages, so please come and visit us.
On August 6, we will be at Smile Garde from 6:45 p.m., and at 8:05 p.m. we will be at Sky Stage.
And on August 6, we will have a live performance by Ukka at 8:05 p.m. on the Sky Stage.
Yay!
Thank you very much for the opportunity to perform on 5 stages this time,
Thank you very much, this is the first live performance of our 9th anniversary,
Please come and join us. Please come and enjoy the show.
Next up,
This way, please.
Yes, on August 12 and 13, we will be performing at the Miniature Appa Festival in Osaka.
Then, on Thursday, August 17, we will be at the Neo Katsudo.
And on Saturday, August 26, we will perform at At Jam Expo 2023.
There will be many live events in August,
We hope you will come and visit us. We look forward to seeing you there.
We will be selling our goods at BiF, so please come and get them.And please get the goods we have for sale at BiF .
That's right. Yahana-chan says let's go wild, so please go wild in a good way.
In a good way.
Let's have a fun summer.
Ah~
How did you know that we wanted to drink watermelon juice?
In the comments section.
There it is.
Yes, I did.
The watermelon juice has arrived.
Thank you very much.
Watermelon juice.
May I have some?
Bon appétit.
I'm so far away from you.
I've never had it before.
I didn't know they made watermelon juice.
And it's not a smoothie.
It's my first time. Be careful not to spill it.
I'm going to eat it.
It's really watermelon.
Smoothie?
Sorry. Oh, it's gone.
Thank you very much.
Watermelon.
Is it in the book?
What? While you're drinking.
Okay, let's get to the rankings.
Let's begin.
I'd like to start the ranking.
I would like to start the ranking. No. 5
Mr. Torikago. Thank you very much.
No. 4Fourth Place
Mr. Satoshi Suminoi. Thank you very much.
Third place, Mr. Riku. Thank you very much.
Second place, Mr. Hiroshige. Thank you very much.
First place, Risaku-san. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
So, the next broadcast will be on August 16, Wednesday at 7:00 pm.
Please click the heart mark and register as a favorite so that you don't miss next week's show.
Also, I stopped my personal distribution yesterday, so please check back everyone.
Please do.
So, that's the end of the 188th edition of Ukka's Delightful and Fufu Showroom.
The end.
This delivery is a review session this time, but we want everyone to do it too.
So please watch this video as well.
Please do.
So, from here, it has already started, but Uka will be at summer festivals and so on,
I will be running through the summer, so please support us all.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Please keep these dates.
I'm asking you all to keep this in mind.
So, are you all right now?
Yes, I am.
That's all I have to say.
That's all for now.
Wait a minute. I want to put out a bibylon towel.
Everybody, Vaibyrho!
I'll get it out!